おっ　当たる
Hot dog! It's got sweet accuracy.
結構当たるじゃん
Okay, I'm next.
よし　次俺ね
But dang, this is light!
それにしても軽いなー
XMBなんて初めて撃つぜ
--My hate of weapons hasn't changed any.
--This is the first I've ever shot an XM8.
武器に対する憎しみに全く変わりはない
Jonah!
ヨナ
ココとしゃべる時の
When I chat with Koko,
I still get this strange feeling
that she is bewitching me.
化され続けているかのような妙な感覚もだ
I traveled with a weapons dealer.
僕は　武器商人と旅をした
We have always stood on the borderland.
我們始終踱步於境界線之上
I'm enjoying the view from here.
皆因此境風景獨好
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe...
Eeny,meeny,miny,moe...
一，二，三，四...
much the same
其實都一樣
We have always stood on the borderland.
我們始終踱步於境界線之上
日听   yaya
I'm enjoying the view from here.
皆因此境風景獨好
日听      奶昔
神
岛
&
诸
恶
魔
Pike or shield?
Pike or shield?  負けたくはない　でも傷つけたくもない
矛 or 盾？ 不想認輸 可是又不願受傷害
I don't want to lose,
but I don't want to hurt anyone either
时轴      小瑾
I took it so I could confirm
手に取って　確かめてた
先挑一樣在手中仔細掂量
That there's definitely no going back
きっと戻れないんだって
可是發現再要反悔為時已晚
Whose side are you on?
你選的是哪邊？
翻译  TL旧民
(Don't want to know!) Memories are shackles
Don't want to know!  思い出は枷
Don't want to know!  思念是枷鎖
注释   TL旧民
(Don't want to know!) A postscript love
Don't want to know!  後付けのlove
Don't want to know!  追悔莫及的愛
后期  aoi
(Don't want to know!) Your kindness is a disservice
Don't want to know!  優しさは仇
Don't want to know!  溫柔是弱點
We have always stood on the borderland.
我們始終踱步於境界線之上
压制   娜夏
With your arms out wide, keep balanced
広げる両手　keep balance
張開雙臂保持平衡
Go the direction that lets you fly higher
より高く飛べる方へ
向著更高的天空振臂而飛
I want to protect
守りたいよ 僕らの翼のないこの背中に背負った
唯獨想保護的是.. 背負於我們那折翼的背膀之上的
What our wingless backs here bore:
Reality and Dream
Reality & Dream
真實 & 夢想
Reality and Dream
Reality & Dream
真實 & 夢想
Reality and Dream
Reality & Dream
真實 & 夢想
Koko, are you going to do some farm work?
ココは畑仕事でもするのか
Agriculture? Out here?
こんな場所で農作業
What could I possibly harvest?
何が収穫できるというのか
If I'm not careful,
the ocean sun will turn me bright red.
海の日差しに気を付けないと
私は真っ赤っ赤になってしまうのです
Koko, it's the captain.
ココ　船長です
--Wow, cool! You can shoot one-handed!
おお　すげえ　片手撃ちか
--A freighter?
--Wow, cool! You can shoot one-handed!
貨物船
Right, right. I mentioned it this morning.
そうそう　朝言ったやつ
Someone from HQ is going
to pick up our left-off cargo.
積み残した荷を本部のものが持ってくる
ん　誰じゃ
Who could it be?
Hello!
もしもーし
ああ　え　うん
Eh? Uh-huh. It's been ages...
久しぶり
Eh? You're on board?
Uh-huh, uh-huh. Got it.
え　乗ってるの
うん　うん　分かった
Later...
じゃ
What's the matter, Koko?
どうしたんですか　ココ
Th-This is bad!
ヤ
ヤバーイ
My big brother is coming! He's on that ship.
兄さんが乗ってくる　その船で
Wilee, hide Jonah!
ワイリ　ヨナを隠して
Teach him language studies.
Don't let him out of the room!
語学の授業をして部屋から出さないで
Roger.
了解
What's the bad situation she mentioned?
ヤバイって　何がヤバイんだ
I think we're always in a tight spot.
いつだってヤバイじゃないかな
But I figure it'll be okay
since we don't have to gear up.
ま　俺らが武装しなくていいってことは大丈夫ってことじゃないか
Come on! Let's begin class.
さ　授業を始めよう
双子でもないのに
You still look identical,
even though you aren't twins.
相変わらずそっくりですね
Of course, you're way better, Koko!
もちろんココの方が最高ですが
Hey, Koko!
や　ココ
Kasper!
キャスパー兄さん
VL MICA missiles...
VL·ミカ·ミサイル
--Will they sell?
--Chequi!
売れるの
That's not an issue.
I've already received the money.
売れるもなにも代金もらってるし
I just have to deliver them.
届けるだけ
What are you doing in Africa?
どうしてアフリカにいるの
Work. I heard you got caught.
ヤボ用
向こうで捕まったって
The CIA's Scarecrow, eh?
CIAのスケアクロウか
It means, "Scarecrow in a field of gold."
黄金の畑の「カカシ」って意味だよ
He was a screwball, wasn't he?
メチャクチャなやつだったろう
But he's good at raising money.
でも　金策の才能があるので捨てずに重宝されていて自由がきく
The States puts up with
his crap since he's so handy.
He's persistent. He'll chase you
no matter where you go,
しつこいぞ
どこまでも追ってくる
despite being a "scarecrow."
案山子のくせに
I don't care!
どうでもいい
"Arms dealers are the only ones who
may spout out contradictions," eh?
「矛盾したことを喋っていい職業は武器商人だけ」
なるほど
I see. That sounds like something Koko would say.
ココさんらしい言葉だな
Contradiction: Something that is inconsistent.
「矛盾」　つじつまが合わないこと
Something that is incoherent.
話の筋が通らないこと
Write "contradiction" three times.
Contradiction
三回ずつ書け
By the way, in China
they have a thing called "folklore."
余談だが
中国には「故事」というものがあり
They can express classics and
morals with just a few characters.
古典や教訓話を　たった数文字で表したりする
"Pike and Shield."
This is a story about a weapons dealer.
これは武器商人の話だ
Once upon a time,
むかしむかし　その商人は人を集めてこう言った
a weapons dealer gathered
some people together and claimed,
"This pike is amazing!"
この槍はすごい　なんでも突き通す
"It can pierce through anything."
Next he showed them a shield and said,
次に盾を見せて言った
"This shield is amazing!"
この盾はすごい　どんな攻撃も弾き返す
"It can deflect any attack."
Then one of the on-looking men said,
すると　それを見ていた男が言った
"Then use that pike to
pierce through that shield."
では　その槍で盾を刺してみろ
The weapons dealer was in a bind.
商人は困ってしまった
Well? Sound interesting?
どうだ　興味あるか
I guess it's mildly interesting.
まあまあ面白いかもね
華僑
Overseas Chinese?
Chinese are all over the world, aren't they?
華僑なんて世界中どこにでもいるでしょう
Who is the dealer allied to?
どこのバンの商人
It's unknown where his "bonds" lie.
どこに絆があるかは不明
And when we say "dealer,"
we mean a "bad dealer," Koko.
そして僕らが商人と言ったら
悪い商人だよ　ココ
I never saw anyone like that.
それらしいのはいなかったよ
You'll definitely run across
him on the African continent.
アフリカの陸では確実に出くわす
Watch out for the overseas Chinese.
華僑に気を付けろ
Officially, he runs the trading
company Da Xinghai Company.
表向きは貿易会社
大星海公司
兄さんがそう言うなら　それはそれはすごい悪もんだ
That coming from you,
he must be one nasty guy.
Well, it's about time I left.
じゃ　そろそろ帰るよ
あ　その前にトイレ借りてもいい
But can I use the restroom first?
Don't ask for permission over every single thing!
いちいち許可を求めないでよね　そんなこと
Jonah, you're enthusiastic
when it comes to language studies.
ヨナ君は語学の授業は熱心だよな
Tojo was complaining that
you're quick to skip out on math.
算数は速攻でサボるって
トージョが嘆いてたぜ
I'm not very good at math.
算数は今一だ
I hear you! I wasn't very good at it, either.
分かるよ　俺も数学は今一だ
I hope you learn how to
read books of all kinds soon!
早くどんな本でも読めるようになるといいな
Books are nice. They don't have just one answer.
本はいい
答えがひとつじゃない
Each and every person who reads a book--
それこそ読む人ひとりひとりの…
The john.
トイレ
Are you ditching class?
サボるのか
I really have to go!
本当にトイレだ
Wilee, long time no see!
ワイリさん　お久しぶり
Kasper, you're here?
キャスパーさん　いらしてたんですか
Good to see you. It's been ages!
これはどうも　お久しぶりです
あ　しまった
Crap! This is what she meant!
こういうことだったのか
But I can't tell him not to enter the restroom!
しかしトイレに入るなとは言えないし
Kasper!
キャスパー
I'm glad to see you're well, Jonah.
元気そうでよかった　ジョナサン
Let go of me, Chequita!
離せよ　チェキータ
This image of a boy with a knife saddens me.
お姉さん悲しいわ
「少年とナイフ」な構図
My sadness triples when that image
それも一挙動で振り抜けるテクを伴うと
accompanies an attack
you intend to follow through with.
悲しさ三倍もしたわ
I want you to drop the knife.
あなたこそ　ナイフを離しなさい
For the record, this toy cannot kill anyone.
あとこんなおもちゃじゃ人はやれない
It will merely cost you some fingers.
自分の指が飛ぶだけよ
Use a long-handled knife with a full tang.
ヒルトの高いフルダングのナイフを使いなさい
Ask Valmet for further details.
詳しくは　バルメに聞くことね
Chequita, Chequita!
チェキータさん　チェキータさん
Lecture him or advise him, but pick one.
説教かアドバイスか　どっちかにしてください
That was just a little hello, wasn't it, Jonah?
今のなんか挨拶だもんな　ヨナ
After all, he's a warrior capable
of fighting on par with me now.
彼はもう僕と対等に戦える戦士なのですから
Didn't we first meet about three months ago?
三ヶ月ほど前か
君との出会いは
I see you have kids here, Vice Commander.
子供がおりますな　副司令
He's a soldier.
あいつは兵隊だ
When we recently asked HQ for more men,
この間本部に増員を頼んだら
they only sent over one brat from the Alpine Unit.
山岳部隊から一人だけ寄こした
The other kids here are orphans.
ほかにもいるが
それは孤児だ
Gasud, I accept your proposal.
ガスード　提案に乗ってやるぜ
I have heard that the influence
of this nation's policies
この国の政策の影響で
いままで武器の供給は止まるという話は知っていた
is going to sever our
ongoing flow of weapon supplies.
In which case, we are justified
in seeking weapons from the west.
ならば　西側の武器を模索するのは正当な行為だ
Exactly.
そのとおりです
However, I am only going through
with this because you have served
ただし　これは
お前があの有名なキャスパーの長年の部下っつーことだから動く話だぜ
under the infamous Kasper for years.
Let me see Kasper.
俺をキャスパーに合わせろ
もちろんです　キャスパーはこの土地に強く注目しています
But of course. Kasper has
a keen interest in this land.
Well, let us go.
さ　行きましょう
ただし　私の荷物は困った場所で立ち往生していますが
However, I am afraid my baggage
is stuck in a most unfortunate location.
I understand.
分かってる
That Yasuf Gasud guy...
あのユスフ·ガスードってやつ
Who is he really?
正体は何なんだ
I don't buy that he's a newspaper journalist.
新聞記者なんて絶対嘘だ
副司令がきた
The Vice Commander's coming!
Malka, hide the food!
マルカ　ご飯を隠して
You eat like pros even though you don't work!
働きもしねえが食うのが一丁前かよ
You and you! Come with me.
お前とお前　付いてこい
Go on.
おい　は
Yes sir!
Those aren't the eyes of a normal person!
普通の人間の目じゃない
Wait! I'll go, too.
待て　僕も行く…
Don't give a superior officer lip over his orders!
長官の　命令に
口出すんじゃ　ねえ
I'm going to leave without you.
置いてきますよ
He doesn't even know basic conduct!
こういう基本がなっていねえ
Jonathan!
ジョナサン
--This was the last I ever saw of Malka.
これが僕が見ているマルカの最後の姿だった
--Jonathan!
--This was the last I ever saw of Malka.
ジョナサン
Malka...
Malka's... Malka...
マルカ　マルカが…
I should have gone with her!
マルカ　ついて行けばよかった
What happened out there?
行った先で何が起きた
I know all too well. They made Malka...
分かりきったことだ
マルカは　兵たちの代わりに地雷原を歩かされ
...walk through a minefield
instead of using soldiers.
Malka...
マルカ　マルカ　マルカ
Malka...!
Malka, you poor thing!
かわいそうだ
Maurice, listen to me very carefully.
モーリス　僕の言うことをよく聞いて
いいかい　まず子供のみんなを秘密基地に
Listen. First I need you to take
all of the children to our secret base.
絶対に出ちゃダメだ
Don't go out, no matter what.
おい　貴様
Hey, punk!
Huh?
No matter what.
絶対にだよ
It's the enemy!
敵だ
What's going on?!
何事だ
--Where are the enemies?!
--I can't say. I don't see--
分かりません
誰も姿を…あっ
--Keep moving!
--I can't say. I don't see--
Hey, whoa! Is this for real?
おいおい　マジかよ
Where's it coming from?!
今のどこだ
Don't fire! You're going to shoot allies!
やめろ　同士撃ちになる
Don't blindly shoot around!
早く行け
Hey, isn't the fighting getting closer?
おい　近づいてきたんじゃねえか
Quiet!
黙ってろ
I don't believe it!
信じられねえ
Why can't we see them?!
全然姿が見えねえってどういうことだよ
Don't shou--!
でっけえ声出すな
Oh, I found one!
いたぞ
I will avenge you, Malka.
仇を打つよ　マルカ
Someone report the situation!
誰か状況をしめせろ
Hey, anyone will do! Is anyone there?
おい　誰でもいい　誰かいないのか
Have you identified the enemy yet, Fatso?!
まだ敵の正体わかんねえのかよ　デブ
お前の正体は何なんだ
Who are you really?
お　俺は　武器商人だ
I-I'm a weapons dealer.
H-Hey, could you spare my life?
な　なあ　命は助けてくれないか
If you do... I know!
そうしたら　ほら
All of this will be yours.
これは全部君のものだ
I don't need money.
お金なんていらない
マルカを返して
Give Malka back!
M-Malka? What's that?
マルカ
何それ
Maurice, look after the kids...
モーリス　子供たちを…
Killing intent! It's heavy and sharp... Wolves?
殺気だ
重くて鋭い
狼？
音がしない
It's silent. They're humans!
人間だ　基地にいた人
Are they from the base?
いや　感じが全然違う
No, it doesn't feel like them at all.
I'm surrounded!
囲まれてる
Hello, Soldier Boy.
ハロー　ソルジャーボーイ
Clear!
クリア
Nice! You have good intuition.
いい感じ
感も息もよくて
You're just like a mishka.
まるでミーシャのようだよね
Going by the aftermath,
行動の跡から考えるに
I believe that child attacked
the entire base in order to kill Gasud.
その子がガスードをやるため内部から基地をまるごと襲撃したと
He has rendered the base inoperable.
基地の機能は停止しております
Amazing!
すごーい
I'm Kasper Hekmatyar, an arms dealer.
僕はキャスパー·ヘクマティアル
武器商人だ
Who're you? You aren't in these records.
君は
この資料に載ってない
And this even lists the four orphans...
四人の孤児のことまでは書いてあるのに
あんたの名前はなんてーの　だってさ　ミーシャ
He's asking for your name, Mishka.
There are only three children now.
子供たちは三人になってしまった
Gasud killed Malka!
マルカをガスードが殺したんだ
I see. Now I get the picture.
なるほど
事件の全貌がつかめたよ
So, how do you feel? Satisfied?
…で　君は
気が済んだのかい
You managed to avenge Malka,
マルカの仇討ちをやり遂げたじゃないか
even though it meant involving
just about everyone in the base.
基地のほとんどの人を巻き込んでまで
I understand.
分かるよ
You made a pre-emptive strike
out of fear of someone stopping you
標的にたどり着く前の横ヤリを恐れた先制攻撃だ
before reaching your target.
After all, it'd defeat the point if you got killed.
自分が死んだら元も子もないもんな
See, I have a younger sister.
僕には妹がいてね
Both my sister and I were born
on a container ship out at sea.
兄弟二人とも海上のコンテナ船に生まれて
We followed our parents,
bouncing from country to country.
親にくっついて　国を転々とした
I have countless fake passports and
national registries, but no hometown.
偽のパスポートや国籍はいくつもあるが
故郷がない
I have no idea what patriotism is all about.
愛国心と言われてもなんのことやら
Yet even someone like me
slightly questions your methods,
そんな僕でも
同胞まで撃った今回の君のやり方
since you killed your comrades in that escapade.
ちょっとだけ疑問に感じたのさ
That's it.
それだけだ
Despite that, I don't have any
suggestions for what you should have done.
かといって　「こうすればよかったのでは」なんて案も出ないよ
Don't sweat it.
気にするな　戦場には答えの出ない疑問が溢れている
The battlefield is overflowing
with unanswered questions.
Gasud's death worked out
all right in the end, too.
ガスードの死も　結果オーライだよ
I don't need a subordinate who can't do his job.
お使えのできない部下なんていらない
I wasn't trying to sell them weapons.
僕は武器を売ろうとしたのてはない
I was trying to slowly dissolve them
with the enticement of weaponry.
武器で誘惑して
ジワジワと溶かそうとしたのだ
A military-only road that will
cross the nation is in the works.
この国を横断する軍用道路の建設
This base was in the way
of laying down the foundation.
その基盤作りにこの基地は邪魔だった
Surging waves of oil, soldiers, and
weapons will flow along that road.
それは怒涛のように石油と軍人と武器が流れる道
It will lead this country to prosperity.
この国の繁栄への道だ
A road? Malka died over a road?!
道
マルカは道なんかのために…
Anonymous Boy Soldier, I know
that anger makes you stronger.
名も知らぬ少年兵
怒りは君を強くすることも
I also know that it is not in
your nature to enjoy fighting.
本来なら戦いなど好まぬさかなことも分かった
So what about fear?
ならば恐怖は
I'm going to make you pay
for killing my subordinate.
部下殺しの落し前はつけてもらおう
Fear... How will fear change you?
恐怖は
恐怖は君をどう変化させる？
W-Wait! Are you going to kill them?!
ま　待って
殺すのか
Wait! The kids--!
待って
子供たちを…キャスパー
Kasper!
キャスパアアー
There was nothing but water inside.
中には水しかなくて
I quickly grew too hungry to move.
お腹がへってすぐに動けなくなった
I thought a lot about Malka,
what he said, and what I had done.
マルカのこと
あいつが言ったこと
僕がやったこと
I thought because I was afraid
to lose my ability to think.
とにかくたくさん考えた
何も考えられなくなるのが怖かったから
I didn't think you were still on this ship!
まだこの船に乗ってるとは思わなかった
How dare two grown adults pick on Jonah!
いい大人が二人してヨナをいじめてんじゃないよ
Leave!
出て行け
おらの船から出て行けー
--Get off of my ship!
--Don't push me!
押さないで
--Get your butt in gear!
--My, my.
あらあら　まだ生きてたのね　そこのおじさん
ちゃっちゃか歩け
You're still alive, Old Man?
You're as rude as ever, Chequita.
相変わらず口の悪い女だぜ　チェキータ
Try to play nicely with him, Mishka.
仲良くしてあげてね　ミーシャ
Don't kick me, Koko! You'll make me fall.
蹴らないでココ　落ちるから
Kasper.
キャスパー　僕　いつか必ずお前を…
I swear, someday I will...
See you around, Jonathan.
またな　ジョナサン
Kasper once locked me inside
of a container for several days.
僕は　キャスパーに何日もコンテナに閉じ込められたんだ
I know. I'm really sorry.
知ってる　ほんとごめんね
He's always been like that.
あいつは昔からああなんだ
I did something terrible at that base.
僕はあの基地でひどいことをした
I only kill. I never manage to save anyone.
殺すばかりで　誰も助けられない
There is nothing but sadness.
悲しいことだらけ
As I was starving to death,
空腹で死にそうな中
I thought over and over,
"Does the world hate me?"
「僕は世界から嫌われてるのか」って何度も思った
I'm not really sure why, but...
でもどうしてなのかよくわからないけど
But even so, I love this world.
それでも僕は世界が好きなんだ
How about you?
ココは
I can't answer that question.
その問には答えられない
I'm sorry, Jonah.
ごめん　ヨナ
No, it's okay.
いや　いいんだ
You may as well have answered it.
答えたようなものだ
We aren't in a relationship
where I should have to polish you.
磨いてあげるような付き合いじゃないんだ
But if you rust, I will die.
でも　お前が錆びると僕が死ぬ
Jonah?
ヨナ君
That's strange. Where did he go?
おっかしいな　どこいった
It's time for science.
理科の授業の時間なのに
Have you seen the Little Lady?
I hear she's looking for me.
お嬢を見なかった
俺を探してたらしいんだ
I see... Maybe she's around
the container up front.
そうか
前のコンテナの方か
Oh, right! Mao was searching for you.
そうだ　マオが君を探してたぞ
Uh-huh.
まあね
"Uh-huh"?
You still haven't found Jonah?
ヨナ坊がまだ見つからない
He's running from you, Mao!
そりゃ逃げられてんだよ　マオ
It's just like math time with me.
俺の算数の授業と同じだ
Tojo's right.
東条の言ったとおりだ
Aren't I? He's bad at the sciences.
だろう
理系の勉強が苦手なんだよ
He's a pro at playing hooky.
サボりの猛者だ
Finding him will be impossible
if he's hiding in earnest.
やつが本気で隠れたら
発見は不可能
Th-This is--!
こ　これは…
Uh, it's a Volks-something-or-other.
あえっと　フォルーなんだらよ…その…
It's a car!
車
Since Orchestra trashed the old one,
this is our unit's new car!
前のはオーケストラに壊されちゃったから
我隊の新車であーる
You were amazing behind the wheel back there.
例の件では素晴らしい気転であった
Keep up the nice driving techniques, buddy!
その調子で　ナイスドライブテク頼むよ君
Thank you, Little Lady! You're awesome!
ありがとう　お嬢
さすがだぜ
あ　ヨナを見なかった
Have you seen Jonah?
He just passed by a minute ago.
さっきそこですれ違ったけど
しばらくアフリカだなあ
--We'll be in Africa for a while, huh?
--What of it?
それが何か
Have something you care to say, Lehm?
私に言いたいことでも　レーム
Not really. Since I can't smoke
inside, I came out to enjoy the view
別に
室内禁煙っつって　見晴らしのいいとこ来たら
and you just so happened to be here.
バルメがいたってだけだモーン
Don't get so edgy.
ピリピリすんなって
You've been through a lot in Africa...
バルメはアフリカでいろいろあったもんな
I'll back you up. We are comrades and all.
フォローするぜ
仲間だからな
I'm sure Koko would say the same.
ココだって同じことを言うはずだ
心配いりません
Don't worry about me.
My old scar was just throbbing a little
when we dropped anchor earlier.
先ほど上陸したとき
ほんの少しだけ古傷が疼いただけです
It's true that I will never
forget what happened in Africa,
たしかにアフリカの記憶は忘れられないものですが
but I'm back to my usual self.
もういつもの私です
But having Koko offer me her
support is a pretty nice idea!
でも　「ココのフォロー」ってのはなかなかナイスアイディアです
Koko! Make me feel better!
ココー　私を慰めてええ
--Koko!
--She's one weirdo.
ココー
へ　おかしな奴
Amazing! I should make this
my very own secret place.
すごい　僕だけの秘密の場所にしよう
ジョナサン　僕と君は永遠に分かり合えない
Jonathan, we will never see eye to eye.
No wonder you're strong.
You're a boy soldier sent from the Alpine Unit.
強いわけだ
山岳部隊からの少年兵
I took the privilege of looking into you.
君を調べさせてもらった
I was the one who sold
the cutting-edge weapons to the men
紛争時　君の村を狙う敵に
最新の武器を流したのはこの僕だ
who were targeting your village in a dispute.
Although indirectly, I am
the one who killed your parents.
間接的ではあるが
僕は君の両親の敵だ
You bastard!
この野郎
Are you too weak to bite away my flesh?
噛み切る力がもうないのか
Or are you holding back?
それとも加減か
Right! That is the result of fear.
そう　それが恐怖の効果だ
While fearing death, you thought and thought
君は死の恐怖の中
考えに考え抜いて自分の立ち位置を知ったのだ
until you realized where you stand.
You decided whether you should kill me or use me.
僕を敵に回すか利用するか判断したんだよ
Very well. Let's begin the negotiations.
よかろう　商談を始めよう
I'm sure we can come to some favorable terms
きっと良い条件が出せる
since I like people who know their place.
僕は自分の「分」を知った相手が好きだから
The three children...
三人の…子供たち…
僕が保護してる
I have custody of them.
Send them somewhere safe,
where they can live happily...
あの子たちが安全に　幸せに　生きていけるように
I wander around from
the Far East to here to West Asia.
僕は極東からここ　西アジアを渡り歩く
I'll set them up so they can enjoy
safe lives in a country called Japan.
日本という国で安全な生活が送れるよう工面しよう
Now, what do you have to offer?
さあ　君には何が出せる
I don't have any money...
お金なんて持ってない
I'll buy your fighting skills.
君の戦闘能力を買う
You'll work as a professional bodyguard.
人物警護のプロとして働くのだ　どうだ
Sound good?
Then it's a deal.
交渉成立だ
That sister I mentioned earlier wants you.
以前話した妹が君のことを欲しがっている
I found out through the investigation,
but I want you to tell me your name.
調査で知っているが
改めて名前を聞かせてくれ
My name is...
僕の名前は…
Jonathan Mar, I presume?
ジョナサン·マルク　だね
Nice to meet you, Jonah.
はじめまして　ヨナ
I am Koko Hekmatyar.
私はココ·ヘクマティアル
You have a frozen glare.
凍ったような表情をしているね
I shall melt that ice...
その氷　私が溶かそう
The ocean god reclines against the light,
光横たえる海神
光怪陸離的海底龍神
His mistake wavering along the scar
創痕の間に揺らめく過ち
累累創痕之間搖曳著縷縷罪孽
He rises to the surface and takes a breath
浮上して息を継ぎ
浮出水面 吸清吐濁
For he has obtained a love
and hate that only dissolve and blend
溶かされ混じるだけの憎愛を手にした
愛與恨 如漆似膠 如影隨形
His dream leans toward
矛盾孕む
矛盾誕生
The sound of the scheme
この世界ごと 覆い尽くしてる策動の音に傾く夢
冥冥的夢中 世界漸漸傾浸於欺言詭語之中
That shall encompass this
world fraught with contradictions
He no longer has legs
脚は　もう無い
足膝 已沒入虛無
His heartbeat pierces through the watery wall
水壁を貫く鼓動
透過水壁 傳來陣陣鼓動..
恶魔岛字幕组(bbs.emland.net)
诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)
本字幕由   恶魔岛字幕组   &   诸神字幕组   联合制作
(bbs.emland.net)    (kamigami.org)
翻译 TL旧民        日听 yaya
注释 TL旧民        日听 奶昔
后期 aoi           压制 娜夏
仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
诸神字幕组
恶魔岛字幕组
African Golden Butterflies phase.1
Her name is Koko.
She is loco.
I said, "Oh no!"
Her name is Koko.
She is loco.
I said, "Oh no!"